Jesus, my son, I've been trying to call you all the time, but my network is already so weak, this Wi-Fi doesn't work, it's not that bad.
Paul didn't even turn on the app to test it.
What kind of app is this now? What are you talking about?
It's an African app, producer. Look son.
Yes?
I'm just starting, son.
Yes? And then? Because I'm always like this, I always call you to come and see the Wi-Fi work, and then the man says it works.
And then what does this thing do now?
It doesn't work.
Wait, what does it do?
It says it doesn't work.
What did you say? Our farmers can't do that. What is this app's name?
Cruiser.
Okay, show me, can you share it with me?
I can, yes. I think if you look here and press here, so.
Yes? Oh, that's to see if you can get better Wi-Fi there.
Yes.
Oh, there you can share it.
And if we just change the number, like that.
Yes?
And then send it to us.
Okay. And then, what then? Can I then save it?
Paul, just click on the link and download it, and then there it is.
Yes, like that. Okay, great.
Thank you, I'm going to download it a little bit, because Yanni, I can't tell more stories for me.
I'm going to make it so I can show it to him.
Cruiser, say for me, this is nothing to worry about, son, this Wi-Fi work.